

SERGEY ILINYKH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT/REDUX/TYPESCRIPT)

CONTACT ME.



Russia, Ekaterinburg



+7 919 381 30 98



s.ilinykh.ekb@gmail.com











PORTFOLIO

PROFILE

Front-End developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux ,HTML,CSS, JS. My free time is dedicated to Codewars and becoming familiar with NodeJS. In the future I see myself as a Full Stack Developer. Ready to consider project work and full-time employment.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

Sept. 2020 to present

- React development using redux, React-redux, react-router-dom, redux-thunk, Axios, Formik, Material-UI libraries.
- · Work with Hooks, TypeScript.
- Refactoring, bug fixing, migrating to TypeScript, registration and login form creation Reusable components development, jest testing.

POLICE PSYCHOLOGIST

Ministry of Internal Affairs | Dec 2012 to present

- Working in extreme conditions
- Organization of moral and psychological support in the department
- Analysis and assessment of the socialpsychological climate of the collective and the moral and psychological state of the personnel
- · Psychological counseling for employees

SKILLS

- REACT
- TYPESCRIPT
- REDUX
- AXIOS
- REST API
- JAVASCRIPT
- MATERIAL-UI
- HTML & CSS
- UNIT TESTS
- STORYBOOK

EDUCATION

IT INCUBATOR
Frontend developer
May 2020 to Sept. 2020

• URAL INSTITUTE OF HUMANITIES Psychologist, Teacher of Psychology Sept. 2010 to June 2015

LANGUAGE

English upper-intermediate (in progress)